https://bafl.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Baltic News
Contact
Baltic American Freedom League PO Box 65056 Los Angeles, California 90065-3651 | Phone: (323)255-4215 | Email: info@bafl.com
Skip to content
We won’t sell or trade your info!
Privacy on BAFL-Baltic American Freedom League: www.bafl.com are part of a non-profit organization and as part of its mission. Unless otherwise stated, for the purposes of this privacy policy the Baltic American Freedom League will be referred to as “Us” or “We.”
Subject to the privacy limitations inherent with email and non-secure Web sites, We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This document outlines our privacy policy and explains what We do with the personal information that We collect from users of this Site.
We update this privacy policy from time to time and these changes to the privacy policy will be posted on the Site. It is your obligation to review this privacy policy. If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you may contact us via email at info@bafl.com.
What information is gathered about you and how do We use it?
If you use any of the special services available through the Site, you will be asked to submit certain information, names and email addresses. This information is used to permit you to receive any information you may have requested from us and any additional communications our organization may deem appropriate in relation to your request.
When you send a message, sign a petition, request membership, donate, submit your email information through www.bafl.com, We may ask for your name, address, e-mail address and other optional information that you may choose to provide. We also collect and store the full text of the message you send through our service. This is necessary to deliver your message and to identify you to the recipient.
User hereby releases the Baltic American Freedom League from any liability or damages arising from the use or publication of any of User’s letter(s)/information contained on/submitted to www.bafl.com.
We will place a cookie in your browser to remember your personal information. This cookie is a file that contains your name, address, and e-mail address information as you entered it on the message form. The next time you send a message, We will retrieve that information from the cookie and automatically enter it on the message form for you. A couple of things to remember about cookies:
Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when you’ve received one.
Will We disclose any of your personal information?
We may disclose your name, address, phone number and e-mail address to the recipient of the message you send through our Site. This information is required because most government officials and media contacts will not accept messages they receive from unidentified correspondents.
We will not disclose any information about individual users, except as described in this Privacy Statement, or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of The Baltic American Freedom League.
We will not share, rent nor sell the information you provide. We may disclose aggregate, non-personal information about Site users in order to describe our organization to third parties, and for other lawful purposes.
Will We use your information for direct mailings/emailings?
You are using the Site to engage in civic participation, which is the mission of the Site. Occasionally we may send you a message or mail regarding legislation, events, or news that might be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such messages, simply send an e-mail to info@bafl.com with “remove me from the bafl.com list” in the subject line.
In addition, We may contact you via e-mail for the following reasons:
To send you a copy of a message you have sent through our web site.
To send you information about events or legislation.
If you send us a message about the Site, is it private?
There is an area on the Site which permits you to submit messages, and other information. Any feedback included becomes the property of The Baltic American Freedom League; We may use your feedback to make improvements to the Site, or to contact you.
What else should you know about your privacy?
Keep in mind that your name, address, and e-mail address, as well as any information about yourself that you include in the messages you send through the Site, will be read by the recipient of your message and/or his or her staff. That’s really the point of the Site – to enable you to communicate with us. Remember that whenever you disclose personal information in your messages you send to others, that information can be collected and used by the recipients and may even be forwarded to other parties.
FURTHERMORE, WHILE WE DO OUR BEST TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE CANNOT ENSURE OR WARRANT THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION YOU TRANSMIT TO US, AND YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK.
Children’s Privacy Statement
This children’s privacy statement explains The Baltic American Freedom League’s practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.
This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site.
Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.
Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of a child under thirteen in the Site’s online activities on providing personally identifiable information.
Questions Regarding Privacy
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices, or your dealings with us, please contact us by writing to:
Baltic American Freedom League PO Box 65056 Los Angeles, California 90065-3651
Email: info@bafl.com
Join our Mailing List Click here to sign up.
Baltic Caucus Click here to visit the House Baltic Caucus Website.
October 2020  (1)
June 2020  (1)
January 2020  (1)
March 2019  (2)
February 2019  (1)
July 2018  (3)
June 2018  (1)
May 2018  (3)
April 2018  (16)
March 2018  (17)
February 2018  (5)
January 2018  (5)
November 2017  (7)
October 2017  (12)
September 2017  (1)
August 2017  (4)
July 2017  (8)
June 2017  (8)
May 2017  (4)
April 2017  (4)
March 2017  (8)
February 2017  (3)
January 2017  (10)
December 2016  (5)
November 2016  (6)
October 2016  (7)
September 2016  (6)
August 2016  (12)
July 2016  (19)
June 2016  (17)
May 2016  (15)
April 2016  (15)
March 2016  (10)
February 2016  (18)
January 2016  (10)
December 2015  (12)
November 2015  (12)
October 2015  (9)
September 2015  (8)
August 2015  (6)
July 2015  (7)
June 2015  (14)
May 2015  (8)
April 2015  (28)
February 2015  (12)
January 2015  (10)
December 2014  (20)
November 2014  (5)
October 2014  (10)
September 2014  (23)
July 2014  (2)
June 2014  (7)
May 2014  (13)
April 2014  (13)
March 2014  (28)
February 2014  (6)
January 2014  (8)
November 2013  (1)
October 2013  (1)
April 2013  (10)
March 2013  (3)
February 2013  (15)
January 2013  (8)
December 2012  (6)
November 2012  (10)
October 2012  (18)
September 2012  (5)
July 2012  (9)
June 2012  (10)
May 2012  (6)
March 2012  (4)
February 2012  (13)
January 2012  (15)
December 2011  (13)
November 2011  (17)
October 2011  (17)
September 2011  (13)
August 2011  (18)
July 2011  (16)
June 2011  (14)
May 2011  (21)
April 2011  (8)
March 2011  (2)
February 2011  (1)
January 2011  (8)
December 2010  (5)
November 2010  (7)
October 2010  (13)
September 2010  (3)
July 2010  (3)
June 2010  (1)
April 2010  (1)
March 2010  (2)
February 2010  (3)
January 2010  (7)
July 2009  (1)
April 2009  (4)
March 2009  (3)
February 2009  (7)
January 2009  (20)
December 2008  (19)
November 2008  (22)
October 2008  (36)
September 2008  (24)
August 2008  (59)
July 2008  (24)
June 2008  (25)
May 2008  (34)
April 2008  (18)
March 2008  (35)
February 2008  (31)
January 2008  (42)
December 2007  (1)
November 2007  (8)
October 2007  (22)
September 2007  (15)
August 2007  (11)
July 2007  (7)
June 2007  (11)
May 2007  (20)
April 2007  (15)
March 2007  (11)
February 2007  (17)
January 2007  (23)
December 2006  (10)
November 2006  (7)
October 2006  (14)
September 2006  (11)
August 2006  (7)
July 2006  (14)
June 2006  (5)
May 2006  (16)
April 2006  (15)
March 2006  (24)
February 2006  (13)
January 2006  (25)
December 2005  (6)
November 2005  (7)
October 2005  (11)
September 2005  (6)
August 2005  (7)
July 2005  (16)
June 2005  (17)
May 2005  (17)
April 2005  (13)
March 2005  (9)
February 2005  (10)
January 2005  (11)
December 2004  (4)
September 2004  (1)
June 2004  (1)
May 2004  (1)
April 2004  (2)
March 2004  (6)
February 2004  (2)
December 2003  (2)
November 2003  (4)
October 2003  (3)
September 2003  (1)
August 2003  (6)
July 2003  (6)
June 2003  (1)
May 2003  (4)
April 2003  (2)
March 2003  (6)
February 2003  (7)
January 2003  (7)
December 2002  (1)
November 2002  (2)
October 2002  (4)
September 2002  (3)
July 2002  (1)
Baltic American Freedom League PO Box 65056 Los Angeles, California 90065-3651
Phone: (323)255-4215 | Email: info@bafl.com
